{
    "subject": "Warren_Beatty",
    "predicate": "produced",
    "object": "Reds__film_",
    "human_readable": "Warren Beatty produced the film Reds.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9177191257476807,
            "question": "Was Warren Beatty involved in the making of Reds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9099939465522766,
            "question": "What film did Warren Beatty produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8995367288589478,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Warren Beatty."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8925221562385559,
            "question": "What is the title of the film produced by Warren Beatty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8737451434135437,
            "question": "Is Warren Beatty known for producing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8664206266403198,
            "question": "Who produced the film Reds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7192705869674683,
            "question": "What year was the film Reds released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5964630246162415,
            "question": "Besides acting, what other role did Warren Beatty have in filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5658107399940491,
            "question": "What genre is the film Reds?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26373639702796936,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors who starred in Reds?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Warren Beatty produced the film Reds.",
            "html": "yago_21488_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Reds?",
            "html": "yago_21488_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides acting, what other role did Warren Beatty have in filmmaking?",
            "html": "yago_21488_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Reds released?",
            "html": "yago_21488_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21488_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21488_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21488_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21488_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21488_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21488_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21488_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21488_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21488_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21488_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. In fact, there are multiple mentions of Warren Beatty's involvement with the film Reds as its director, co-writer, producer, and star."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states, \"Reds is a 1981 American epic historical drama co-written, produced, and directed by Warren Beatty,\" which supports the triple that Warren Beatty produced the film Reds."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}